probably get you a few items for profit
from moneycontrol prove for
moneycontrol.com joins us to talk about
a stock that she's tracking rather
closely Neha
today's topic is icse lumbar General
Insurance the growth in Gross direct
premium income for ICC alone but was
higher than the industry growth in the
first nine months of the current fiscal
which improved its market share as of
December ends along with Organic growth
the acquisition of bharti EXA has also
helped ICC Lombard to consolidate its
Market position as the second largest
General insurer while the motor
insurance which is the largest segment
for icsl Lombard from muted business
health insurance was the key driver of
overall growth since health insurance
segment has a higher profitability as it
has lower planes ratio as compared to
motor insurance uh the ICC Lombards
combined ratio trended downwards in the
current fiscal management indicated that
combined ratio can go down further in
fy24 as the investment made towards
enhancing the distribution network will
start
start getting reflected in the form of
lower expense ratio all this put
together implies that return on Equity
uh which has moderated to mid-teens from
around 20 in the previous fiscal can
start improving from fy24 onwards in
terms of valuation the stock is
currently trading at around 5.3 times
trailing Book value which undoubtedly is
Rich despite the price correction
however since a general insurance is a
structural growth story investor can
keep this stock on their radar
all right Tanya thanks a lot for that
we'll step into a short break on the
other side we'll be focusing on a bunch
of stocks which are in Focus uh hero
motocov Royal Orchid and I'll tell you
why these stocks are buzzing